I broke Jake's jaw.
His teeth look a bit removed as well.
Yeah, his teeth have come out of place.
But credit to him, he done well.
But I told him what was going to happen.
Why does he look like that?
People will criticize you for going six rounds with Jake.
How does he, no, not him.
No, not him.
Why?
What's he?
Why he look like that?
I put myself in the shoes of a coach.
Why does he look like that?
Do y'all see that?
That's, yeah, yeah.
That's a special type of fine.
Even from the back.
Damn.
Okay, what's he saying?
And there was a bit of a mix.
I said to myself, I'm not going to knock you out.
I am going to systematically punish you round after round.
And like, I wanted to, I wanted it to be slow and my follicle.
Right.
I swagged.
Yeah.
But I dropped down now.
That's him.
And I just kept on hitting him.
What a sport.
I hate you for everyone in England.
I was hitting him.
Lift every voice and sing till earth and air.
I think you'll find, sir, that there will come a time when black people wake up and become
intellectually independent enough to think for themselves.
But as other humans are intellectually independent enough to think for themselves, then the black
man will think like a black man.
And he will feel for other black people.
And this new thinking and feeling will cause black people to stick together.